[
  {
    "question": "What’s the best thing about Switzerland?",
    "answer": "I don’t know, but the flag is a big plus.",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "I invented a new word!",
    "answer": "Plagiarism!",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "Did you hear about the mathematician who’s afraid of negative numbers?",
    "answer": "He’ll stop at nothing to avoid them.",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hear about the new restaurant called Karma?",
    "answer": "There’s no menu: You get what you deserve.",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do we tell actors to 'break a leg?'",
    "answer": "Because every play has a cast.",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the best thing about Switzerland?",
    "answer": "I don’t know, but the flag is a big plus.",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvordan navngiver man en kineser?",
    "answer": "Man smider en stegepande ned af trappen og hører hvilken lyd den giver",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvorfor sad appelsinen og pæren alene i mørket?",
    "answer": "Fordi pæren var gået",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvad sagde Jesus da han satte sig ind i taxaen?",
    "answer": "Sømmet i bund",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvad får man vis at man blander Donald Trump og Hillary Clinton?",
    "answer": "En racistisk dukke",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvad kalder man en blondine der farver sit hår brunt?",
    "answer": "Kunstig intelligens",
    "categorie": "Normal",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bear is the most condescending?",
    "answer": "A pan-duh!",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of noise does a witch’s vehicle make?",
    "answer": "Brrrroooom, brrroooom.",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s brown and sticky?",
    "answer": "A stick.",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "Two guys walked into a bar.",
    "answer": "The third guy ducked.",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you get a country girl’s attention?",
    "answer": "A tractor.",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "en"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvorfor er det at fisk er så grimme?",
    "answer": "Det er jo selvfølgelig fordi at de er van(d)skabte",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvad er det mindst talte sprog i verden?",
    "answer": "Tegnsprog",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvad sagde den ene cykel til den anden?",
    "answer": "Styr dig!",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvad fik den lille kannibaldreng, som kom for sent til aftensmaden?",
    "answer": "En kold skulder",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "da"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hvorfor skulle skyen i skole?",
    "answer": "Fordi den skulle lære at regne",
    "categorie": "Dad",
    "language": "da"
  }
]
